[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "Waht is C++ ?",
"a": "Movie",
"b": "OOP",
"c": "Number",
"d": "Nitric",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "Which operator adds values ?",
"a": "-",
"b": "+",
"c": "/",
"d": "*",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "C++ extension is ?",
"a": "Cpp",
"b": "Cxx",
"c": "Txt",
"d": "Exe",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Which one is loop ?",
"a": "if",
"b": "Cout",
"c": "While",
"d": "Cin",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Which is a Keyword ?",
"a": "Start",
"b": "Loop",
"c": "While",
"d": "Print",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "To read input from user ?",
"a": "Cout",
"b": "Input",
"c": "read()",
"d": "cin",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "To display output ?",
"a": "cin",
"b": "show",
"c": "cout",
"d": "print()",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Which keyword ends a loop ?",
"a": "end",
"b": "break",
"c": "stop",
"d": "quit",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "Which is a logical operator ?",
"a": "=",
"b": "+",
"c": ">",
"d": "&&",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "Which is a valid loop ?",
"a": "switch",
"b": "case",
"c": "if",
"d": "for",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
}
]